JUDE CLARK

Duluth, GA 30097

Phone: 678-825-JUDE (5833) | Email: judeclark2019@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/jude-clark-89262634/ GitHub: github.com/judeclark19 | Portfolio: judeclark19.github.io/portfolio-2/

SUMMARY

Full-Stack web developer with experience in client relations, administration, and systems analysis. A natural problem solver with excellent language skills; including listening, comprehension, and clear expression. Excels in a position that involves solving both daily problems with a high level of detail as well as larger, more complex issues.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Applications: Visual Studio Code, Google Chrome Developer Tools, iTerm2, Git, Node.js, MySQL

PROJECTS

Weather Dashboard - https://judeclark19.github.io/weather-dashboard/

Use this simple weather app to view the current weather conditions, as well as a 5-day forecast, for the city of your choice.

Coding Quiz - https://judeclark19.github.io/coding-quiz/

Try to answer questions about JavaScript within a given time limit. Incorrect answers will take 10 seconds off the clock!

Workday Planner - https://judeclark19.github.io/workday-planner/

Use this planner to write down notes for your upcoming day. Contains one text block for each hour between 9am and 5pm.

EXPERIENCE

Executive Assistant to the CEO

Jar House (Atlanta, GA)

August 2018 - October 2019

- Assisted with ETL of property data for company-wide shift to SalesForce.
- Built custom SalesForce report types to manipulate complex object relationships and produce reports for various departments' needs.

Patron Services Manager

November 2014 - June 2018

Seraphic Fire (Miami, FL)

- Served as the primary point of contact for all external communications, handling all patron interactions with the highest level of professionalism.
- Managed SalesForce database of all donations, donors, and ticket buyers. Assisted with data migration through two complete software transitions of a database containing about 30,000 contacts.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp Certificate — Georgia Institute of Technology AUGUST 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

Bachelor of Music, Music Composition — University of South Carolina AUGUST 2010 - MAY 2014. Summa cum laude